#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ christophschwartz (LinkedIn) www.schwartzpr.de (Company)

#### Top Skills

Media Relations Public Relations Social Media

#### Languages

**Englisch** 

# **Christoph Schwartz**

Managing Director at Schwartz Public Relations in Munich Munich

## Summary

Spezialgebiete: Schwartz Public Relations is an owner-run PR agency in Munich, Germany, specialised in public relations, corporate communications, media relations, social media, internal communications, crisis communication, and corporate publishing. As one of the top10 German tech PR-agencies we consult clients across the entire technology spectrum; IT, eCommerce, telecommunications, consumer electronics, energy, cleantech, medtech, industrial solutions and logistics.

## Experience

Schwartz Public Relations Business Owner 1994 - Present (28 years) Munich

**Managing Director** 

Burson Marsteller Account Director 1992 - 1994 (2 years)

### **ABC EUROCOM**

Account Manager 1990 - 1992 (2 years)

International Public Relations Agency

## Education

Universität zu Köln / University of Cologne Diplom Kaufmann, Betriebswirtschaftslehre (Business Administration) · (1989 - 1991)

Universität Regensburg / University of Regensburg

Vordiplom, Betriebswirtschaftslehre (Business Administration)	· (1987	- 1989)